The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where magic is everything,
there lives one boy who was born without it.
His name is Asta.
His strength and determination helped him become a magic knight.
And despite the many challenges he faces,
he aims for the top and refuses to give up.
Rich or poor, royalty or commoner,
Asta believes anyone can shine.
His mission is to prove that to the whole world
and to become the next Wizard King.
The rest of the Black Bulls and I have been training hard.
We need to be ready to face the Spade Kingdom and that Devil.
But...
The way we are now,
we don't stand a chance against them.
Huh?
Rouge.
There's no time to worry about how I do it.
I just need to do it.
Hmm.
You and I both know there aren't any shops open this late.
Come on. I have a seat.
I'm surprised you're awake.
I walked downstairs.
This bottle of wine was calling out for me.
Hmm.
What is it?
Does it bug you that I'm drinking from your secret stash?
No.
Help yourself.
What?
Not gonna have one?
I'm okay for now.
Though I have always hoped you and I could enjoy a drink together one day.
Just the two of us.
Is that so?
Well, yes.
But I think I might need a rain check.
Alright.
Hopefully next time.
Kay?
Don't push yourself too hard.
Don't worry.
I'll be back in a flash.
Go.
Oh
Hey,
More
Oh
If it's a pain, it's a pain
If it's叶うなら, I'll be with you
This voice, this喉嚨
I call it now
The future, I'll be with you
I'll be with you
To fill my dream
We're going to battle against the Spade Kingdom soon
And the forest of witches may get caught in the crossfire
I am aware
Not only of your plans, but of the deadly threat that will soon befall our home as a result
It was foolish of you to even suggest I wouldn't know that
Then you know that it's serious
These mages possess mana like we've never seen before
And not long from now
Ready or not, we're going to have to contend with them
I'm worried
My friends always push themselves too far because it's the only way they know how to fight
Honestly, it's a miracle we haven't lost anybody because of that
But this time could be different
Your magic already grants you the ability to modify fate, Vanessa
What have you to fear?
Rouge is strong, but there's one problem
If I lose my mana, then she loses her power over fate as well
I've heard about an ancient magic within this forest that only you know
Please teach it to me
If we want to stand a chance in this fight, then I need to harness your power
Even if you were able to wield my awe-inspiring magic, I fail to see the point in this
I just told you the point
If we sharpen our skills, then we might win
That doesn't change a thing
It appears you aren't understanding me
You're right
I'm the one who ran away, so of course you wouldn't help me
It's completely out of line for me to ask you to
But
If I can't become stronger, my friends might be killed
Wait, Vanessa, I'm not saying there isn't a way for me to grant you more power
However, my help does come with one condition
Oh, hello, and you are?
Uh, hi there, Miss Vanessa
It's very nice to make your acquaintance
I'm Samantha
Ah, Samantha
You must be Elvira
The Queen told me about you two
We're doing this on the Queen's orders, understand?
No more, no less
So you're not my superior
All right, I'll remember
Thank you, girls, for leading the way
Look up there
We have security golems on the perimeter of the forest
So we'll know right away if the Spade Kingdom attacks, but...
Right, they react to any threat because they can't differentiate between humans and magical beasts
The Queen has them set to stop firing after three shots as a safety measure
Otherwise, they'd keep attacking forever
I get it
So when Spade does show up here, the golems won't do you much good as a first line of defense
And you're the one who's gonna make them work better, huh?
I mean, you get special treatment from the Queen of Witches herself and all, so you've gotta be pretty talented
I am
But it's more complicated than that
Uh, ma'am?
What's wrong?
I think they just spotted us
Pick them with any offensive spells you know
That should make them run away
Ugh
I'm so sorry
What was that?
I thought you were the amazing hero who defeated the last enemy that invaded the forest of witches
Hmm?
But I guess this time you don't have a bunch of men from the outside world to save you
That what the problem is?
Don't say that, Elvira
It's very rude
Who asked you?
Well, don't you remember what we did during that battle?
Go! Squad 2!
D***
Show them that these witches mean business!
Hey! Stop rehashing the past! It doesn't matter!
Hmm
Oh, I never asked you what type of spells you have
Would you mind showing me?
Right now?
Uh, I guess so
sound magic huh that's all i can do sorry it's no problem what about you
you know how to generate illusions anything else it's not enough excuse me
no i should have asked about that before we started i'm sorry ma'am i don't think i can do this
i mean i'm absolutely useless i'll probably just hold you back i shouldn't be here yeah i bet those
dumb sounds of yours would lead the bad guys right to us let's just go we're nothing but failures
anyway the way samantha panics over every little thing reminds me of gray and elvira is so stubborn
and prideful like noel is at the end of the day there's probably not much difference between them
and the black bulls we might as well wrap things up for now since we've done all we can you're free to
go i'll figure it out by tomorrow sorry again it's not like anything's gonna change
they're useless i can't do this with just them when wartime arrives i'll need as many bodies as
possible so you want me to whip them into shape so they can fight against spade but that's going to
take an eternity wait i get it now you planned this from the start didn't you whatever do you mean
you gave me something impossible to do because you're hoping i'll just give up
tell me what your magic is used for vanessa
hey guess what don't bother we've already heard all about the queen making vanessa train those two
losers it won't work this is elvira and samantha we're talking about the queen's got a sense of humor
yeah vanessa may be little miss special or whatever but this is something not even
she could pull off what a disaster i can hear you guys i guess the witch is here the same as always
i'm so bummed out the cake shop i was talking about closed down oh that's sad
they sure love to talk don't they but i've never been able to participate in their conversations
maybe it's the same for those two tell you what i'll cut you a deal if you purchase it right now
you'll get the exclusive price of 20 000 yule but this offer won't last long so jump on it it's you
oh long time no see girl how have you been domina's here too
that makes sense i knew it would take something major to bring you back to the forest yeah and
what about you well you know my darling other half isn't exactly the most employable guy out there
since he's a wanted man and all he's spending his time on farming at least but it's not enough to
support the three of us so i have no choice but to work my poor little fingers to the bone peddling
these magic items believe me it's a struggle i'm surprised the queen gave you permission
yeah true seeing as how i escaped this place like you did well maybe she thinks letting me sell
my wares here can help her you're good at what you do so i imagine if she lets anyone do it you're
the obvious choice naturally you're in a rough spot though for sure i'm really at a loss here
if that's the case then i think i have the perfect solution huh a magic washboard that removes the
toughest of stains depending on your mana only 80 000 yule for you since we're friends will this
thing really help me defeat magical beasts i don't know ready to check out whoa slow down why would i buy
that thing when i don't even know if it'll be of any use to me hey anything's useful for something
and that goes for people too after all the queen of witches can find a way to use every girl in this
forest to do her bidding right it's as simple as that hmm what is something wrong um no
tell me what your magic is used for vanessa
listen girls i've decided that the three of us are going to rid the forest of those magical beasts
i'm sorry ma'am but i'm really not capable of that this is a waste of time
no it isn't i know we'll succeed why because we're the only ones who can uh you seem weirdly
confident about that what makes you so certain take a look at this map here's the forest of witches
and that's where the monsters are many of the smaller magical beasts like to forage for nuts around
this area and the bigger ones know that which is why they always come here to pick them off
you see this place there are several trees there they're loaded with nuts which means it's a popular
spot for the small beasts and i saw some big ones lurking around as well did you say you saw them
i spent all last night investigating oh wow you looked at me yeah who cares
the rest is easy we have to lead the larger monsters this way before they get too far into the forest
after that we should be rid of them it can't be that simple we're weak there's no way we can control
them it's impossible we can do it just trust me a while ago i felt the same way as you do
i'd given up hope but
wow what happened such pretty dolls they're so tiny think back to when you were first learning to
wield your magic you wondered what it could be useful for everybody wonders that as for me
i wanted to make people smile and that was the one idea i never let go of
and even these days i don't want people to cry i'm glad you like the dolls but wouldn't it be nice
if they had more color and detail
fine if it means that much to you
so cool that's not all these happen to be talking dolls
oh my gosh guys when i went to town yesterday i just had to make a stop at my favorite store
again huh you've been in that place so many times people are gonna think you weren't there
any magic type has multiple uses especially when you combine it with someone else's
we just made these little girls happy and it's all because the three of us put our talents together
everyone ready
it's showtime
yes you're doing great keep it up
stay sharp i know i got it
are we almost there we've been running for a while now
the markers i left last night should be right up here just a bit farther okay
all right this is it
hey what are you doing they're real those aren't the smaller ones that we brought
how do we get out of this all we can do now is run away
we can't give up
elvira make it as scary as you can
if you say so
samantha give it a roar the louder it is the better
okay i'll try
it looks like we did it
it all worked out and we're still alive yep great job
amazing yeah none of us could have done that
but why the queen showed us what you did for the forest
i understand now we're not useless at all
thanks for showing us that it was all you you found something you couldn't give up on
don't let it go not ever
right i happen to know another group of goofballs who never figured out how to give up
anyway
i came back to this place hoping to learn some unbeatable spell but now i don't need it
why is that i'm going to train and bit by bit my mana will increase i'll focus my thoughts on
finding the best way to put my magic to use as long as i keep moving forward and refusing to give
up that's enough instead of fate you tugged at their hearts i didn't realize it but those threads
have always been connected and i had the power to affect both of them so i'll keep fighting to
make sure my friends and the black bulls keep smiling you were completely right when you said
i was mistaken it wasn't only rouge's magic that could change destiny
since i left here i've learned that's up to you he opened the door that's all he didn't change my fate
that was all me i chose my own path and made my own decisions
and i'll keep changing things so that we can all survive this mess
mark my words whatever string of fate leads to everyone smiling that's the one i'll pull
then you must take your leave there's no reason for you to stay
goodbye it was good seeing you
you're going back already yes but first i should thank you too
what do you mean by two oh well whatever if you want to thank me then you should buy this nifty
little guy draw a bath pop this in there and enjoy the bubbles it's the ultimate in self-care trust me
you could use it and the best part is the low low price of just 12 000 yule so how many should i bring
up i don't think i'll be needing any what i'm sure you've made plenty of sales without me having to
buy that thing yeah i have sorry setting up shop here has been really good for me i'm glad the queen
okayed it she might seem like she's all big and bad but she always looks out for us right i guess
say hi to fonzel and mariella for me sure give my love to the black bulls
you're back hey sit down real quick you're up late again huh i was sleeping but i woke up
so you learned any good spells out there nope not a one but i got something i really needed really
compared to your normal pace you still have a lot left in that bottle
you said you wanted us to drink together so i saved some for you i appreciate that
but i think it'll have to wait a while why i need to keep my head clear so for right now it's better if
i hold off okay i get it i'm off to bed i'll see you tomorrow just one more thing what is it
welcome back thanks sir
hello
so
you
Thank you.
Thank you, Queen.
After my talk with you, I know exactly which path I'm supposed to take.
Black Clover, page 140. A favor for Julius.
Wait, I think I see Sally.